

123 Main Street, OrLando, FL 12345 d.tayLor@youremail.com (123) 456-7890 Results-driven senior account manager with over 12 years of experience. Record of building lasting and lucrative long-term client relationships. Strategic thinker with international experience with a focus on consultative selling and territory sales management. Fluent in Spanish, English, French, and Chinese.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SENIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER

Comcast International Orlando, FL I June 2010-Present

- Locate national and international business opportunities for a leading digital accounts agency
- Grow Executive client relationships
- ♦ Secured 10 new clients in 2019, growing the company's revenue by \$3 million
- ♦ Attained 98% client-satisfaction rating and retained 87% of all new clients
- ♦ Assisted in the expansion of Comcast International in the Chinese market, increasing the company's annual profits by \$22 million
- Collaborate with analytics specialists to determine the main causes of client complaints, lowering the number of annual complaints by 16%

ACCOUNT MANAGER

Oceanside Retail, Tampa, FL I June 2008 - June 2010

- Developed and expanded existing sales by 27%
- Negotiated the details of sales contracts with major clients
- ♦ Exceeded all sales goals for the Tampa branch of Oceanside Retail
- Awarded account manager of the year in 2009

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN ACCOUNTING AND BUSINESS MANAGEMENT The University Of Miami, Miami, FI I September 2004-June 2008

KEY SKILLS

- Communication
- Organization
- Presentation
- Public speaking
- ♦ Revenue and profit growth